Guide to the Fashion Moda Archive 1978-1993 MSS 091
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Fashion Moda as a business
  - Subseries B: Grants and Fundraising
    - N. E. A., visual arts, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - N. Y. Foundation for the Arts, 1985-1987 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - NYSCA, application, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - NYSCA, application, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - NYSCA, application, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - NYSCA, application, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - NYSCA, application, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - NYSCA, application, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - NYSCA, application, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - NYSCA, application, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - NYSCA, application, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - NYSCA, architectural application, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - NYSCA, audit, 1989-1991 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1983-1984 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - NYSCA, contract, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - NYSCA, final report, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - NYSCA, final report, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - NYSCA, final report, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - NYSCA, funded presenters, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - NYSCA, funding report, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - NYSCA, slide scripts., undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - NYSCA, South Bronx Show proposal, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - NYSCA: special arts, Marion Brown, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - NYSCA: special arts, Ken Garrett, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - NYSCA: special arts, Barbara T. Smith, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, David Finn, April - May 1984. (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, Nan Goldin, August 1983 - July 1984., 1983 - 1984 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, Charles Hardgrove, March 1-30, 1984. (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project application, Dragon Ilic, September 7-30, 1984. (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - NYSCA: sponsored project funding, 1983- 1984 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Presenting new writers, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Responsibilities of a Director of a New York, New Jersey, or Connecticut Non-Profit Corporation., undated (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Reed Foundation, Inc., 1986 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - South Bronx Cultural Center, 1979- 1980 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Unidentified slide scripts., undated (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Unidentified grant information., undated (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Series III: Artists, Exhibitions, and related material
  Series III is divided into seven subseries and contains 18 boxes of documents. The files are arranged alphabetically and chronologically.
  - Subseries A: Artists Files
    Series III subseries A, Artists Files, contains files Fashion Moda kept on their artists and exhibitions including: resumes, exhibition proposals, plans for exhibitions, consignment forms, program reports, and production materials for exhibitions. Please note that not all of the artists included here actually showed at Fashion Moda.
    - Access Bronx., undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - African Caribbean poetry theater, June 27, 1987. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Agent, announcement., undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Intentionally omitted, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - American Dreaming, December 13 - January 21, 1987. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Andreu, Jose: slides, resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Aone, Toxic, Koor: exhibition, May 1985. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Appropriate Technology Project [see also I. 1. 13], undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Appropriate Technology Project: related newpaper clippings., undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Art et Industrie: contract, October 16, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Art for Money Benefit: collecters, December 4, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Art for Money Benefit: consignment agreements, November - December 1986. (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Art for Money Benefit: correspondence, receipts, and notes, November - December 1986. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Art for Money Benefit: price list, November - December 1986 [see also I. 1. 33] (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Art Womb., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Artist in residence program., undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Artists resumes /Chalfant, Henry, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Barbican Arts Group: proposal, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Brenner, Leslie: proposal., undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Brown, Marion: newspaper article, flyer., undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Chaiklin, Amy: consignment sheet., undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Charles, Andre Pierre: resume, slides, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Intentionally omitted, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Cole, Richard: resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Conde, Richard: resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Corn, Thom: resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Cosentino, Steven: slides, resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Cummings, Michael: exhibition proposal., undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Danceteria, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Dawson, Morris: resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - De Braud, Alberto: resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - [Removed to Oversize], undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Dos Santos, Judith: slides, resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Dragan Ilic: resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - East Village Ladies Salute the Bronx: exhibition, October 24, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Eins, Stefan: resume, reviews, others 1986. [see also over oversize, box 22, also I. 1. 20 and III. A. 4. 75 and 75A] (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Eins, Stefan: notes on Moda, January 1986. (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Eins, Stefan: exhibition posters, see oversize box 22, undated (Box 4, Folder 37A)
    - English, Ron: resume, articles., undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Evans, Andrea: proposal, 1981. [see also over oversize box 22] and Buczak, Brian (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Exhibition, 1981 - 1985 [see also 1. 1. 2 and III. A. 5. 90-93, also pages 20-26 of Finding Guide] (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Exhibition ideas., undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Fashion Moda philosophy [see also I. 1. 1A], undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: artist contracts, November 1 - 16, 1985. (Box 4, Folder 44A)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: artist contracts, November 1 - 16, 1985. (Box 4, Folder 44B)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: notes, misc., November 1 - 16, 1985. (Box 4, Folder 44C)
    - Ronald Feldman Gallery/Fashion Moda benefit: price list, press release, insurance., undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Fiorucci, group exhibition, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Five Boroughs Performance Festival, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Garrett, Ken: slides, resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Garramone, Richard: slides, resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - German artists., undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Golden Door project, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Graham, Robert and Susan Springfield: exhibition, November 30 - December 22, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Grami Gallery: Bogota, Columbia, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Graupe-Pillard, Grace: announcements., undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Headley, Wendell E.: resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Haimsohn, Jane: see III. A. 4. 17, undated (Box 4, Folder 54A)
    - Hertz, Betti-Sue: announcement., undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Hochmuth, Rosemarie: catalog, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Hsieh, Tehching: proposal, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Invitational 1986/87: exhibition., 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Jackson, Isaac: problem, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Januzzi, Angelo: resume, articles., undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Jazz series, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Kahane, Lisa:: many slides in III. F. boxes 7-15 and various in III. C. boxes 5 and 6, 1-54, undated (Box 4, Folder 61A.)
    - Koor: announcement. {slide at III. A. 4. 36], undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Kush & the Nature Theatre of San Francisco: announcement, mailing list, October, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Kaplan, Karen: resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - La Libertad Logico: exhibition, May 17, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Legiardi-Laura, Roland: proposal., undated (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Lehman College, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Levy, Judy: slides, resume, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Live Radio at Fashion Moda, April 14, 1983. [audio cassette] (Box 4, Folder 68a.)
    - Lower Eastside Print Shop., undated (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Lowinger, Leslie: resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Mainland Poetry., undated (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Margot, "Images in Cloth"/Leslie Lowinger, April 15 - May 7, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - Matthews, Joan: resume., undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - Matschiner, Kristl: resume, photographs., undated (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Melamid, Brad: see III. A. 4. 39, undated (Box 4, Folder 74A.)
    - MC TV Channel J: "Making Coincidences", a TV series by Stefan Eins application, contract, funding, 1984 -1988. [see III. G. 16] (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - MC TV Channel J: notes, 1983- 1988 (Box 4, Folder 75a.)
    - Meet the composer., undated (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Meyer, Richard: slides, undated (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - Moda gallery layout, undated (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Moore,Frank: resume, slides, undated (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Mudmen: articles, undated (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Nadel, Jeremy: artist statement, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Neumann, Dolores: see III. A. 4. 17, undated (Box 5, Folder 82A.)
    - New improvements, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Nichols Mural/Print project, 1985 [see also I. 1. 33]. (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Nieves, Hector: photographs., undated (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Owens, A.: artist statement., undated (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Poets and Writers / Baraka, Amiri, undated (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Pollack, Steven: see III. A. 4. 17.., undated (Box 5, Folder 88A.)
    - Poppitz, James: c. v., letters of recommendation., undated (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Program report/exhibition listing, 1981 - 1982. [see also oversize, box 20] (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Program report/exhibition listing, 1983- 1984 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Program report/exhibition listing, 1985- 1986 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Pullen, Don: see III. A. 4. 17, undated (Box 5, Folder 93A.)
    - Quinn, Barbara: resume., undated (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Recchia, Louis, undated (Box 5, Folder 94A.)
    - Rehm, Celeste: slides, proposal., undated (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - RenAva: Christmas cards, undated (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Rollins, Tim & KOS exhibition with also Juma Santos "Journey", January 1985. (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Rollins, Tim & KOS "The Inferno", South-Bronx, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 97A.)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 5, Folder 98-101)
    - Roloff, Stephen: "The broken Wall, budget., undated (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Ryan, Debra Gilbert: slides, resume, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - Sacchetto, Bruno & Nancy Stout: exhibition, March 18 - April 12, 1986. (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - The Salon: announcement mock-ups, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - The Salon: promotional materials, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 106)
    - Sanna, Richard & Heidi Staudt: proposal, slides., undated (Box 5, Folder 107)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 5, Folder 108)
    - "Science, Art, Design, Invention, Technology, Fantasy": production material for book, 1984. [see also I. 1. 29A and III. A. oversize box 21. 114] (Box 5, Folder 109)
    - Schuster, Ilene: resume, catalog., undated (Box 5, Folder 110)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 5, Folder 111)
    - Slide scripts., undated (Box 5, Folder 112)
    - Smith, Mary Agnes: workshop, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - South Bronx Show: 6th annual, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 114)
    - South Bronx Show: 7th annual, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 115)
    - South Bronx Show: 8th annual, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 116)
    - Spank: artist resume., undated (Box 5, Folder 117)
    - Stout, Nancy: announcement, undated (Box 5, Folder 118)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 5, Folder 119)
    - SUNY curate, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 120)
    - Telacopy, September 26, 1986. (Box 5, Folder 121)
    - Tierney, Trin: III. A. 4. 17, undated (Box 5, Folder 121A)
    - Topical Archeology, proposal., undated (Box 5, Folder 122)
    - Touring exhibitions., undated (Box 5, Folder 123)
    - Vienne in South Bronx, Rosa Hochmuth & Lisi Misena, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 124)
    - Wahl, Anita: catalogue, undated (Box 5, Folder 124A.)
    - Wenneberg, Teresa: resume, undated (Box 5, Folder 125)
    - Wheeler, Irene: slides, resume, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 126)
  - Subseries B: Articles, Press Releases, Flyers, and Announcements.
    Series III Subseries B, Articles, Press Releases, Flyers, and Announcements, contains articles, press releases, flyers and announcements for exhibitions at Fashion Moda.
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1981. [see also oversize, box 21] (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1982. [see also oversize, box 21] (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1983. [see also oversize, box 21] (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, 1990- 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Articles on Fashion Moda, n. d. [see also oversize, box 21], undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Articles written by Joe Lewis., undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Press releases, 1979 - 1983. [see also oversize, box 21] (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Press releases, 1984- 1988 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Press releases, 1990-1993 (Box 5, Folder 15A)
    - Flyers, 1979. [see also oversize, box 21] (Box 5, Folder 16..)
    - Flyers, 1980. [see also oversize, box 21 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Flyers, 1981. [see also oversize, box 21] (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Flyers, 1982. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22] (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Flyers, 1983. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22] (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Flyers, 1984. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22] (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Flyers, 1985/1986 [see also oversize, box 21 & 22] (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Flyers, 1987. [see also oversize, box 21 & 22] (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Flyers, 1988. [see also oversize, box 21] (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Flyers, 1989 - 1991. [see also oversize, box 21] (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Flyers, 1992- 1993 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Flyers, n. d., undated (Box 5, Folder 26A.)
    - Flyer mockup, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Flyers for other galleries. [see also oversize, box 21], undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Show announcements, 1980- 1985 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Show announcements, 1986- 1992 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Show announcements, n. d., undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Show announcements for other galleries., undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Subseries C: Photographs
    Series III Subseries C, Photographs, contains photographs covering exhibition openings, artworks, artists, Fashion Moda's neighborhood, and performances.
    - Ahearn, John: cast making., undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Agent., undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Animals Living in the City, Christy Rupp., undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Archeology, Liz n' Val, October 26 - November 23, 1991. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Artist collective & community members video, March 10, 1979. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Aspen Colorado Show [see also I. 1. 34], undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Brasz, Mark, undated (Box 6, Folder 6A.)
    - Buggiani, Paolo [see also I. 1. 7], undated (Box 6, Folder 6B.)
    - California billboards, 1980 - 1981 [see also I. 1. 17 and III. F. 15. slides 36-38] (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Camouflaged Panzerism, undated (Box 6, Folder 7A.)
    - Clark, Elizabeth: "Reconstruction", 1980 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Collins, Marshall: "World of Dinosaur", November 23 & December 6, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Contact Sheets., undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Cooper, Jerome., undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Daze, undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - De Mille, Arnette, undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Dejon, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Dickson, Jane: "City Maze", September 6 - October 4, 1980. (Box 6, Folder 14A)
    - Edwards, Marianne: July, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Expressions Africans, February, 1987 (?). (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Facade [see also I. 1. 40], undated (Box 6, Folder 16A.)
    - Fashion Moda T-shirt, undated (Box 6, Folder 16B.)
    - Fekner, John: "From the Monkey to the Monitor", November 13 - December 4, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Freedom, undated (Box 6, Folder 17A.)
    - Fun Shots, undated (Box 6, Folder 17B)
    - Graffiti Art: Australia, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Graffiti Exhibition, 1980 [see also I. 1. 15 and III. B. oversize 21. 14-18] (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Graffiti Artist's from the Early 70's, May 1984. (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Group shot including Brasz, Daze, Easy-G, Eins ,Haring and Headley, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Holmes, Victor:, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Holzer, Jenny: facade of Fashion Moda [see also I. 1. 22 and III. A. oversize21. 32B], undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Howland, Becky 1981 Image for South Bronx Poster. (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Image for South Bronx Poster, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Jones Baird, Stefan Eins, Mark Kostabi, 1985-1986, see oversize box 21 (Box 6, Folder 25A.)
    - "Ladys Wrestling", June 14, 1980. (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Lorenz, Patrice: "From Farrakahn to Fallwell", 1984 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Lubar, Cindy: "119 Comments", 1981. (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Misera, Lisi:, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Moving Tent, South Bronx, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Music, people & other objects, at exhibition of Haim Steinbach, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Neighborhood, mostly 3rd Ave. Betw. 135 and 165 St., Bronx, NY, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Owens, Ashley., undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Pesce, Victor: "Water colors and drawin", February 28 - March 21, 1981. (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Place, Chuck Hamilton: Spring 1982. (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Polly Ester Nation: "Jesus comes to the Bronx", March 1980. [see also I. 1. 7] (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Poppitz & Santos., undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Reccha, Louis., undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Riviera, James, undated (Box 6, Folder 40A.)
    - Rollins, Tim & KOS, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Rothschild, Gail: "Three Arches", October 6, 1984. (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Sacchetto, Bruno:, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Schecter, Jill, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Science and Technology Exhibition, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 44A.)
    - Sebrens, Sam:, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Schr, Beate Maria: "Bodysuits", 1993 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Smith, Mary Agnes:, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Spank., undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Steinbach, Haim, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 49A)
    - Stout, Nancy., undated (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - South Bronx Show, 1979 (?) (Box 6, Folder 50A)
    - Taylor, David., undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Toral, Tabo [see also III. C. 6. 30], undated (Box 6, Folder 51A.)
    - Vulva, by G. J. W., Fall 1992 [see also I. 1. 45] (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Wells, David: "Cranach Cutouts", 1981, others (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Unidentified photographs., undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Subseries D: Artworks
    Series III Subseries D, Artworks, contains artworks by Keith Haring, Andre Charles, Daze, Crash, Kenny Scharf, Koor, and others. Included here is the Fashion Moda Portfolio with works by Ronnie Cutrone, Crash, Daze, Leon Golub, and James Poppitz.
    - Aone: drawings, incl. for Documenta 7. [see oversize, Box 21- No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Brasz, Marc: drawing., undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Charles, Andre: "South Bronx Show", 1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cooney, Robert: "Por Exxon For Kill". [see over oversize, box 22], undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Crash: drawing for Documenta 7, other [see also oversize, box 21- No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Daze: drawing., undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Eins, Stefan. [see also oversize, box 21], undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Fekner, John: drawing for Documenta 7, others [see also oversize, box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - G-Man, drawing [see oversize, box 21], undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Haring, Keith; drawing for Documenta 7. [removed to oversize Box 21- No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Headley, Wendell: drawings, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Jackson, Isaac: art for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Koor: drawing., undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Kostner, Arthur: drawings. [see over oversize, box 22], undated (Box 6, Folder 13A.)
    - Mullican, Mat [see oversize box 21], undated (Box 6, Folder 13B.)
    - Nenner, Paulette: drawing for Documenta 7[removed to oversize Box 21- No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Pabon, Jorge: drawing., undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Pou, Alyson: collage for Documenta 7 [removed to oversize Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Ramos: drawing., undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Satanic Show [see also I. 1. 21], undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Scharf, Kenny: drawing for Documenta 7. [removed to oversize Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Steckel, Anita: photograph for Documenta 7. [No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Thomas, Kathleen: drawings., undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Toxic: drawing. [see oversize, box 21], undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Unidentified drawings. [see also oversize, box 21], undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - van Dalen, Anton: drawing for Documenta 7[removed to oversize Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 6, Folder 23A.)
    - Wells, David: drawings for Documenta 7. [removed to oversixe Box 21 - No Duplication Allowed], undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Y-Pants, drawing, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Fashion Moda Porfolio with works by Ronnie Cutrone, Crash, Daze, Leon Golub, and James Poppitz. (In Mapcase), undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Subseries E: Printed Materials
    Series III Subseries E, Printed Materials, contains magazines, journals, and catalogs on artists such as Mark Kostabi, Ron English, Nancy Stout, and Amy Chaiklin. These items were found in the collection and do not necessary pertain solely to Fashion Moda.
    - Art Com: number 16, v. 4 #4, 1982. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Bomb: Spring/Summer 1985. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - The Bride Groom is Hear, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Chaiklin, Amy: "Wall-painting" book, 1983. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - [item removed]., undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - English, Ron: "Art is a Horrible Waste of the Imagination", 1988. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Events, New Museum: New York, 1981 [see also I. 1. 16] (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - [item removed], undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Galleria Communale d'Arte Moderna, Bologna: "Arte di Frontera", March- April 1984. (Box 6, Folder 9)